Yakant Idol
Q.Please give the title call to QUTE.
My three main elements
I think this might really be the first time I've been called QUTE!
Really?
Not really. They didn't say that to me at Takoyaki Raymond either.
You weren't in charge of QUTE?
No, I was not in charge of QUTE.
What was he in charge of?
I don't know.
Uh... a wild one?
Okay, so that's how it's going to be.
I'd like to move on to the three main elements of Flash Time.
This is the section where we ask you to introduce the three elements that affirm you.
Now, let's take a look at your 3 elements, Mr. Hori. Here you go!
Here they are.
Yes!
Games, ramen noodles, and alcohol!
You look like a bachelor group to working people.
Well, I don't like to go out much.
I don't like to go out so much, so I do all the things I can do at home.
Games
Games.
What kind of games are these?
There are many, but the one I'm most addicted to.
I've died in my sleep playing Monster Hunter.
Most recently Monster Hunter.
I've got Sun Break, but I've been playing it on the Switch since Rise.
I was playing it with the staff and performers of "Ohayo Asahi Saturday Desu" every day until morning.
We played games every day until morning.
It really is Ohayo Asahi, isn't it?
That's right! We played until the sun came up.
That's amazing.
I was addicted to it.
I was also addicted to Fortnite.
All the Hud members moved from MonHun to Fortnite.All the Hud members were moving from MonHun to Fortnite.
We played that all the way until the morning.
You know how much time you spend playing games?
Yes, yes, yes.
How many hours?
But I moved to Fortnite in the middle of the day.
I ended up playing about 450 hours.
That's amazing.
I was really into it.
Did you like games before you got into MonHun?
But I liked it.
But have you heard of PUBG, which is played on cell phones?
Yes, yes, yes.
Like wilderness action?
Yes, of course.
I was really into that kind of stuff.
But I also liked the lighthearted games on the switch.
Like Atsumori?
I love Atsumori too.
Action games...
The only game I got really into was MonHun.
I'm playing games with the staff at Bevy right now.
I've heard that you've been playing with the staff of Bebaby.
When you were working as Takoyaki Poverty, did you play games with other members?
Yes.
Among the members.
But we were all geeks of some sort.
Yes, yes, yes.
We were all in different genres.
Sakura was into comedians...
I was really into bands and stuff, but
Karen was into music and arts...
We were all geeks in different genres.
That didn't change at all.
That's why we didn't work together or anything.
I don't know.something
Oh, like Mario Kart.
Mario Kart with all the members?
I love Mario Kart.
Who was the strongest in Mario Kart?
They were all weak.
Everyone was weak?
Everyone is weak.
It's a mud fight.
Muddy match?
Yes, sir.
It's like someone's running the other way.
What a waste!
Someone take it to Tokyo.
This show...
Kogezaka-san
Takuya-san
Nanosan
Mizusan
Ayana-chan.
Thank you very much for watching!